Downloaded from
YTS.MX
(grand orchestral fanfare
playing)
Official YIFY movies site:
YTS.MX
♪ ♪
(wind whistling)
(grunting)
♪ ♪
(all grunting)
(distant shouting)
(machinery clacking)
(bleating)
-(bleating): H-Hey.
-H-Hey.
(wind whooshes)
♪ ♪
(low growling)
(growling)
(gasps)
(distant screaming)
(screaming)
(growling)
That's right. It is I, Tai Lung.
It can't be.
(roars)
(rams clamoring)
I have returned
to take what is mine,
which is
everything that is yours.
(yelling)
(gasping)
(all gasping)
Let it be known,
from the highest mountain
to the lowest valley,
that Tai Lung lives.
And no one
will stand in his way.
Not even
the great Dragon Warrior.
♪ ♪
(kids laughing)
Oh, where is Po?
He was supposed to be here
hours ago.
Ping, will you
please just relax?
I am relaxed!
Okay. I'm sure Po is fine.
But what if he's sick?
What if he's hurt?
What if he's hungry?
-(whimpers)
-Don't get your noodles
in a twist.
If I know our son, he's probably
just kicking back
and catching some rays.
♪ ♪
(echoing):
Kung fu!
(gasps) That's bad.
Oh, getting worse.
(roaring)
Ooh! (grunting)
Ah, come on!
(grunts)
(all gasping)
(gasps)
(roaring)
(screaming)
(grunts)
(yelling)
Ha-ha!
Okay, big guy, we're really
gonna have to wrap this up.
(warbling)
Whee!
-Oink! Oink!
-(cheering)
-Again, again!
-That was fun.
-Let's do that again.
-(Po laughs)
And next time,
keep your surf off their turf.
(all cheering)
I'm late. I'm late.
Ooh, I'm late.
(excited clamoring)
It's the Dragon Warrior!
Was, is, and always will be.
We love you, Dragon Warrior!
Oh, and I love you, too,
adoring fan.
-Sign my scroll.
-Sign my hat!
-Sign my shirt!
-PO: Okay, okay.
I'll sign whatever you want.
-Po.
-(clamoring stops)
Master Shifu.
Here, let me just...
Uh... There.
That's, uh, much worse.
-We have to talk.
-Absolutely. Let's talk.
Right after the ceremony.
-Let's go!
-(cheering)
Ceremony? What ceremony?
PO:
The Staff of Wisdom,
-given to me
by Master Oogway himself.
-(crowd aahing)
It is said that
whoever possesses this staff
has the power
to travel between the realms.
The power to unlock the door
to the Spirit Realm.
And now, the power to open
the all-new Dragon Warrior
Noodles and Tofu!
(cheering)
Where the broth has kick...
-(all exclaiming)
-...and the bean curd's
a knockout.
(cheering)
(sputtering, whistling)
Dragon Warrior!
Will the Furious Five
be here, too?
Unfortunately, no. They're off
on super cool kung fu missions.
Tigress is taking on
the free-range chicken gang.
-(clucking)
-Monkey's hot on the trail
of the missing macaque.
Crane was crowned king
of the Crocodilians.
-ALL: Crane!
-PO: Long story.
Viper's wrapping up
peace talks
between the cobras
and the mongooses.
Or is it "mongeese"?
And Mantis?
Well, he's just trying
to keep his blushing bride
from biting his head off.
Just 'cause
they're not here in person
doesn't mean they're not here
as life-size cutouts.
Now, who wants a picture?
-(cheering)
-Okay, okay. One at a time.
-Oh, me, me, me! Me!
-Uh, you.
-KID: My turn, my turn!
-And then you.
(all gasping)
(Shifu groans)
He really captured
your disapproving scowl.
We need to talk.
-Now.
-(gasps)
Hey, can I get one of those
in a wallet size?
-SHIFU: Po!
-Coming!
Do you remember the first time
you climbed these steps
to the Jade Palace?
(panting) How could I forget?
I thought I'd never
make it to the top.
Yes, but you persevered,
and once again,
destiny calls for you to take
the next step on your journey.
The next step?
What are you talking about?
I've already taken
all the steps, haven't I?
It is time for you
to choose your successor.
-Successor for what?
-A successor
to be the next Dragon Warrior.
(laughs) Yeah, I get it.
Funny, 'cause
I'm the Dragon Warrior.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, wait, wait.
You mean I'm not gonna be
the Dragon Warrior anymore?
-Exactly.
-Then what am I gonna be?
Once a successor is chosen,
you will advance
to the highest level
in all of kung fu.
Spiritual Leader
of the Valley of Peace.
Whoa!
I don't know what that means.
It's just like
Master Oogway before you.
You will oversee the valley,
passing along wisdom
and inspiring hope.
Look, I appreciate
the promotion.
I think
I'm just gonna stick with
the whole Dragon Warrior thing.
"Dragon Warrior thing"?
What is it you're holding?
A cookie.
Other hand.
The Staff of Wisdom.
-It was given to you
by Master Oogway.
-Ah!
Do you really think
it was so you could
open a restaurant
or pose for pictures?
He wasn't super specific.
Oogway entrusted you
with that staff
so you could follow
in his footsteps
and become something better
than you already are.
You take it.
No. Oogway did not
give it to me.
Being the next Oogway
is not my destiny,
which I have accepted
and am at peace with.
-Really, it's fine.
-You don't sound fine.
You don't sound fine!
I'm very fine!
-Okay, okay. You're fine.
-This is an honor.
Oogway chose you
as his successor,
and now you must choose yours.
Master Shifu, I finally found
something I'm good at,
and now you want to just
take it away from me?
No one is
taking anything away, Po.
Who you are will always be
a part of what you become.
Yeah, but where's
the "skadoosh"?
You know what I mean?
The "shasha-booie"?
I don't want to seem ungrateful,
but I don't know
anything about passing on wisdom
or inspiring hope.
All I know are two things:
kicking butt and taking names.
And if I'm being
completely honest,
I'm not even that good
at the name-taking.
Like, who is that
fire-breathing crocodile?
I want to say Steve.
You were chosen to bring peace
to the valley.
And there are other ways
to bring peace
than simply kicking butt.
Well, sure,
but not any fun ones.
Please.
Being the Dragon Warrior
is all I know.
-It's who I am.
-Not anymore.
The Valley of Peace
needs a spiritual leader,
and Master Oogway chose you.
You'll start
interviewing candidates
first thing tomorrow morning.
Candidates? What candidates?
(crowd cheering)
♪ ♪
(crowd aahing)
Awesome!
-No way!
-(cheering, applause)
-(chuckles): Wow!
-(cheering)
Skadoosh.
Fantastic pose.
(screaming)
(crowd gasping)
(cheering, applause)
Woo-hoo! Nice!
(clangs)
Master Po will now choose
the next Dragon Warrior.
-(cheering)
-(rhythmic drumbeat playing)
CROWD (chanting):
Dragon Warrior! Dragon Warrior!
Dragon Warrior!
(music and chanting stop)
So many great candidates.
I'm gonna let the finger decide.
Wait.
Whoa, whoa. What is happening?
The Dragon Warrior! It's me!
(cheering, whooping)
(groans)
(shrieking)
SHIFU: Like it or not, Po,
you have to choose a successor.
Eh, nothing about them
says "dragon" or "warrior."
You will know when you know.
How do I know when I know?
-You know?
-(sighs)
When I'm conflicted,
I come here to ask the universe
for answers,
just as Oogway did before me.
I'm not conflicted.
I'm just not ready
for a next step.
What is that you're holding?
-The Staff of Wisdom.
-Other hand.
A chewed-up peach pit?
Exactly.
Every pit holds the promise
of a mighty tree.
Uh, how is this gonna
help me find answers?
Don't ask me. Ask the universe.
Be the pit, Po. Be the pit.
(straining):
There we go.
All right, universe,
give me some guidance.
Inner peace. Inner peace.
Inner peace.
Dinner, please.
Dinner with peas.
Snow peas
in a sesame soy glaze.
(frustrated grunt)
Inner peace. Inner peace.
(inhales deeply)
This is not working at all.
Maybe focus on your breathing.
I'm trying,
but it's kind of hard
when you keep talking to me.
Technically, you're talking
to you, if you think about it.
Hey, will you two be quiet?
I'm trying to concentrate here.
Wait, if I'm Po's inner voice,
then who are you?
Uh, I'm Po's inner-inner voice.
How many voices
do I have in there?
-You do not want to know.
-This dirt is itchy.
-I just love kung fu.
-What am I gonna be?
Are we alone in the universe?
(voices overlapping, clamoring)
-(high-pitched yelling)
-Anyone want a cookie?
(wind whistling softly)
♪ ♪
Universe?
Is that you?
(gasps)
(chokes)
(grunts, coughs)
(sputters)
Attention, mysterious figure.
The Dragon Warrior is here
to perform justice.
(exclaims)
I know you're in here.
Just a matter of time
before I find you.
Ooh.
(grunts)
Ha!
You can't hide
from justice forever.
(gasps)
The Dagger of Deng Wa.
You've got excellent taste,
I'll give you that.
But I can't give you that.
Give it back.
If you insist.
(exclaims)
Oh, no.
He's got a walking stick.
What are you gonna do,
stroll me to death?
This stick is not
for the strolling.
It's the Staff of Wisdom.
The Dragon Warrior
is gonna be mad
when he finds out
you took his stick.
I am the Dragon Warrior.
I'm just gonna say it.
Nothing about you says
"dragon" or "warrior."
(grunts, yells)
(grunts)
(distorted):
Whoa.
(exclaims)
How dare you desecrate
the Hall of Heroes...
Who's desecrating what now?
(grunts)
Master Ostrich's Egg!
Oops. My bad.
Hi-yah!
The Indestructible Chain Hammer
of Master Pangolin.
Whoopsies.
(straining)
Ha-ha! Ooh. Oh!
(grunting)
(giggles)
The Urn of Whispering Warriors,
which I've already broken.
Twice!
Why would you keep
an urn of souls?
Feels kind of creepy.
(whispering warriors gasp)
(sighs)
Are you doing okay there,
big guy?
You're looking a little tired.
I've never felt more awake!
(grunts)
The War Hammer
of Master Chipmunk?
(whispering warriors groan)
You're gonna pay for that.
(gasps)
Hello?
(whispering warriors booing)
You faker.
It's not faking.
It's called Method.
Catch you later, panda.
No.
(whimpers)
I think I'll catch you now.
(shouts)
(grunts)
-(shouts)
-Whoa!
-(grunting)
-(Po laughs)
-(exclaims)
-(grunts)
Whoa!
Told ya.
You got me, oh great
and powerful Dumpling Warrior.
That's Dragon Warrior-- Ah!
Let go of me.
Just tell me one thing.
How did someone like you
become the Dragon Warrior?
That's a mystery
for you to solve
during your two-year stay
at the Valley of Peace prison.
Valley of Peace prison? (scoffs)
Sounds like a day care.
It is a day care
on the weekends.
But it's also a prison.
RAM:
There he is!
-Dragon Warrior!
-Tai Lung is back.
Tai Lung has returned?
He demanded all of our iron,
then destroyed our quarry.
He's supposed to be
in the Spirit Realm.
-Well, he's back.
-He said that
he's not gonna stop
until the Valley of Peace falls
and the Dragon Warrior
-bows before him.
-He's back.
-Please, you got to
do something.
-It was Tai Lung.
Looks like I'm not
the only one around here
with a mystery to solve.
Well, you know what they say.
Every step leaves a footprint,
no matter how small.
(wind gusting)
♪ ♪
PO:
Every step leaves a footprint,
no matter how small.
Very clever, fox.
You know something.
Maybe I do, maybe I don't.
Okay, I do. I really, really do.
-Tell me.
-And why should I?
I mean, what's in it for me?
The peace of mind knowing
you did the right thing.
You're adorable.
Has anyone ever told you that?
And I don't mean just in, like,
in the cuddly sense.
I don't have time for games.
Tai Lung is running loose
in the Valley of Peace!
Maybe. Or maybe she wants you
to think it was Tai Lung.
-Wait. "She"?
-Mine.
The empress of disguise,
capable of taking any form,
mimicking any shape.
The master of deception.
The lizard of lies
with the glowing teal eyes.
I'm talking 'bout...
The Chameleon.
(gasping)
This is kind of
a private conversation.
(squawking)
Who's The Chameleon?
Only the most powerful
shape-shifting sorceress.
So she's shape-shifting
into Tai Lung!
But what does she have against
me and the Valley of Peace?
These are good questions.
You should ask her.
You're right.
How do I find this...
The Chameleon?
She isn't someone
who can be found.
At least not without someone
in the know.
And how do I find
someone in the know?
Oh, it's me.
It's obviously-- It's-it's me.
I'm in the--
I mean, I'm in the know.
Forget it.
I'll find her on my own.
Good luck.
After all, how hard can it be
to find someone who can look
like anyone, blend in anywhere?
Fine. You lead me
to The Chameleon,
and I'll see what I can do
about reducing your sentence.
Deal.
-(door opens)
-SHIFU: Po!
What do you think you're doing?
(stammers) Th-There's this
shape-shifting sorceress
on the loose and...
That's a job
for the Furious Five.
Well, they're not here.
And someone needs to protect
the Valley of Peace.
Look, I know
that change is difficult
and that you enjoy
being the Dragon Warrior,
but your job
is finding a successor.
The Dragon Warrior
and I have a deal.
Mind your own business,
squirrel.
Master Shifu is not a squirrel.
I'm a red panda.
You know what?
I love that for you.
Po, this is your decision.
But I think you know
what choice Master Oogway
would want you to make.
♪ ♪
-Thanks for the free stay.
-SHIFU: What are you doing?
-Little dank for a day care.
-Wait.
Not bad for a jail.
-Where is she going?
-You can't leave.
Don't worry. I'll have her back
before you even know
she was gone.
You are supposed to be
passing along wisdom
-and inspiring hope!
-(guard grunts)
Just think of it as one last
Dragon Warrior adventure.
I'll be back soon.
Tell my dads I love 'em.
I can't hear you anymore!
-Bye!
-(squawks)
(Shifu groans)
Yeah!
It sure is good
to be a free fox again.
-That's a good back scratcher.
Yoink!
-Hey!
So does this really unlock
the door to the Spirit Realm?
It doesn't work like that.
It has to be given
in order to gain its powers.
Gotcha. Given to gain.
-So, uh, can I have it?
-No!
-What do you take me for?
-An easy mark.
What's an easy mark?
Someone who's easy
to steal from.
Usually because they're generous
and too trusting.
-Like you.
-Aw, thank you.
I heard The Chameleon
is a monster
with an appetite
of a thousand predators.
And her favorite food is panda.
They say this Chameleon
character has magical powers.
If you say her name three times,
she'll take you away
in the night!
(kids crying)
The Chameleon can shape-shift
to look like anyone.
-Even you.
-Or you.
(chewing noisily)
Mr. Li, Mr. Li, is it true?
Po's going to take down
an evil sorceress?
The-The Chameleon?
(chuckles): Well, a Dragon
Warrior's work is never done.
Li, I'm thinking Po teaming up
with a convicted felon
to take down an evil sorceress
wasn't such a great idea.
Relax. Po has faced demons,
demigods and everything else
in between.
He's always come out on top.
Ah, you're right. You're right.
But what if you're wrong?!
Calm down, Ping.
How bad can
one evil sorceress be?
Who is she to summon us?
Classic power move.
We're the heads of
Juniper City's
most prominent crime families.
And she's just some bug-eyed,
power hungry reptilian runt.
You left out
the evil sorceress part.
We used to run this city.
Now we pay her
half the money we swindle.
It's like a criminal can't make
an honest living anymore.
Yeah, but what can we do?
Together, we can take her down.
-(bosses gasping)
-Are you nuts?
She's a shape-shifter.
She could be at this very table,
and we'd have no idea.
For all we know,
you're The Chameleon!
Or you're The Chameleon!
-Or maybe...
-Oh, no.
-...maybe...
-Don't say it.
(voice changing):
...I'm The Chameleon.
I said don't say it.
(bosses gasping)
We obviously spoke out of turn.
Sorry, Chameleon.
No, no, don't apologize.
You and your families prospered
by preying upon the weak.
So it doesn't feel good when
you're the one being squeezed.
Especially when
the one doing the squeezing
is just a "bug-eyed,
power hungry..."
What was the rest?
Reptilian runt.
Well, this reptilian runt
wants more.
You already have the city.
What else
could you possibly want?
I have something special
in mind.
I'm very close to achieving it.
As close as the blood moon.
But the blood moon
is two nights away.
So little time,
so many expenses.
Which is why
I'll need to increase
this month's tribute to 60%.
No.
What was that, now?
I mean no disrespect.
Don't worry.
I forgive you for the impudence
and the backstabbing
and the blatant disrespect
you've shown me.
I forgive.
But I never forget.
You might say
I have the memory...
Oh, don't say it.
...of an elephant.
(grunting)
(deep grunting)
(trumpets)
(bosses gasping)
(deep voice): You think
I've pushed you too far?
Then you, my friend, can't begin
-to fathom...
-(grunts)
...just how far I can push.
(exclaims, grunting)
(bosses whimpering, muttering)
(normal voice): I'll expect
your tributes by dawn.
(birds chirping)
Are we gonna stop
for lunch soon?
Justice doesn't stop for lunch.
But it does take the occasional
time-out for snackage.
Want to split my almond cookie?
You're just gonna give me
half of your cookie
-out of the goodness
of your heart?
-Mm-hmm.
What's the catch,
the rub, the bamboozle?
-The "bam-what-le"?
-You know, the fleece,
the rook, the flimflam.
Do you want the cookie or not?
(chewing noisily)
(mouth full):
I got my eye on you.
How much farther is it
to this The Chameleon?
Just a little farther.
♪ ♪
(crickets chirping)
(both screaming)
Li, what are you doing out here
in the middle of the night?
Well, I... I-I didn't want
to miss the blood moon rising.
Oh, pooh.
You are just as worried as I am.
All right, all right.
I know pandas come across
as calm, gentle and chill,
but (chuckles) the truth is
-I'm kind of freaking out!
-So am I.
Po is just too calm,
gentle and chill
to face
a shape-shifting sorceress.
-What if he's captured?
-What if he's tortured? (gasps)
BOTH:
Our baby!
Okay, okay.
Maybe Po has
finally met his match,
but there is still something
that he has
-that The Chameleon does not.
-What's that?
Us.
Now, let's go find our son.
I hope Po's okay.
You know, Li,
a wise goose once said,
"Worrying doesn't make
the broth boil any faster."
LI:
Who was that idiot?
PING: Me, of course.
I was the wise goose.
LI:
Oh, yeah.
PO:
Whoa!
That's the biggest village
I've ever seen.
ZHEN:
That's no village.
That's Juniper City.
That's where I'll find
The Chameleon, huh?
Just a boat ride away.
And I'm gonna lead you
right to her front door.
Are you sure we'll find
a boat captain in there?
For the right price,
those cutthroats
will take us anywhere
we want to go.
Of course,
we could always opt for
the four-finger discount.
No stealing.
"The Happy Bunny Tavern."
Well, that sounds inviting.
(screams, grunts)
Anybody lose a rabbit?
(whimpers)
(patrons murmuring)
(groaning)
-Stir faster!
-(gasps)
Welcome to
the Happy Bunny Tavern.
I'll find us a ride.
Maybe you can get us some food.
And stay out of trouble.
Hey, what you guys playing?
Mah-jongg.
And the stakes are high.
Can I play?
Surely you'll go easy
on a beginner,
'cause I'm very beginning.
(snickers)
Hey there.
-What can I get you?
-A boat ride to Juniper City.
Ask this guy.
-Who's he?
-He's the captain.
Thanks.
(sighs)
Oh, I win again.
Beginner's luck, I guess.
Never played before, huh?
I'm sorry, are you
accusing me of cheating?
I would like to speak
to the manager, please.
I am the manager.
I'll give you a boat ride
to Juniper City,
but I won't carry
anything illegal.
I don't want any trouble.
(chuckles) Trouble runs from me.
-(squawks)
-Then it'll cost you double.
I'm confused. Should I have
said that I like trouble?
In that case,
it'll cost you triple.
Oh, uh, maybe we can go back
to the double price.
You got a deal.
Great. Do I shake his hand
or your hand?
Can I get anything else
for you, ma'am?
Yes. Everything, again.
Except for the broth.
It was very bland.
-Keep stirring!
-(screams)
(whimpers)
Whoa! One of everything
is my go-to order.
But how did you pay for this?
Legally, lawfully,
fair and square.
-I'm proud of you.
-(grunts)
-(gasping)
-(snorts)
(Zhen gasps)
(growling)
Oh, wow. Look at the time.
Remember we have to do
that thing
-down by the place
with that guy?
-(grunts)
Did you actually think you could
grift a meal out of me?
(gulps) There's got to be
some sort of
misunderstanding here.
(growling)
And apparently,
I'm the one misunderstanding.
Please allow us to pay
for our meal and yours, too.
I'm only hungry for...
-Dumplings?
-...vengeance.
Well, then, come and get it.
No! No, no, no, no!
Don't come and get it!
-Destroy them!
-(shouting)
(grunting)
(screaming)
I got it!
(grunts) Hi-yah!
-Whoa!
-There you go.
(grunts, exclaims)
-All better.
-(screams)
Come on.
Gotcha.
-Keep stirring!
-(whimpers)
(grunting)
(high-pitched scream)
Hi-yah!
(shouts)
(henchman groans)
(exclaims)
Whoa! (screams)
(clamoring)
I'll take that.
Think this belongs to you.
(growling)
Hi-yah!
(coins clinking)
No stealing. (exclaims)
(grunts, screams)
(sighs)
Yeah, I think it's
a little too late for that.
It's never too late
to do the right thing.
-(groans)
-Get them!
-(gasps) Watch out!
-Whoa!
HENCHMEN:
Huh?
(exclaiming)
-Skadoosh!
-(roaring)
(henchmen shouting)
-(henchmen groaning)
-ZHEN: Whoa. Nice move.
You got to teach me that.
GRANNY BOAR:
You die, panda!
(exclaiming)
(yelling)
(grunts)
(screaming)
(screams)
(grunts)
ZHEN:
(screams) Whoa, whoa, whoa!
(screaming)
Who designs a tavern on a cliff?
I shouldn't have eaten
all those dumplings. (yelps)
(grunts)
Huh? Uh-oh.
(both scream)
(grunting)
(squawks)
Sail ho!
(pillars creaking)
-(all exclaiming)
-GRANNY BOAR: Back up!
Move, move, move!
(quacks)
Uh, not that I'm worried,
but what if The Chameleon
knows we're coming?
Why, she could be anywhere.
Anyone.
Li, would you please show
a little backbone?
I'm sorry, but bravery was
never really my specialty.
(quacks)
You don't have to be brave.
You just have to act brave.
Act brave. Got it.
(gasps, screams)
Oh! Oh! Li!
(whimpering)
-Hold on!
-Hold me, Ping!
-It's all been for nothing!
-Please, no!
I'm too young!
-Oh!
-(thump)
How was that for acting brave?
(sighs) Keep working on it.
(sighs) Juniper City.
It's gonna be great
to be back home again.
Does your family
live there, too?
They would if I had a family.
It wasn't easy being
a little fox in a big city.
So I had to survive
any way I could.
-Hey!
-Grifting.
Shilling. Gaffing.
Stop running. Stop running!
Whoa. You're an orphan? So am I.
Well, I mean, I was.
My goose dad adopted me,
and then later,
my panda dad found me.
Goose dads, panda dads.
Guess it takes all kinds.
-Right, Mom?
-(squawks)
Then, one day,
a local took me in,
put a roof over my head,
gave me clothes to wear,
food to eat.
After that,
I was never alone again.
-I guess we both got lucky.
-I guess.
Hey, tell me something.
-Back in the Valley of Geese...
-Peace.
...what did that
angry little squirrel mean...
-Red panda.
-...when he said
you had to find your successor?
(sighs) Now that I'm supposed
to become Spiritual Leader,
I have to find
a worthy successor
to take over
as the Dragon Warrior.
Once you're on top, that's
where you want to stay, right?
No, it's just that--
What do I know about
being a Spiritual Leader?
I can't even come up with
one of those
cool-sounding proverbs.
"Life's greatest enemy is..."
Uh, I don't know. Stairs?
Okay.
-Everyone knows life's greatest
enemy is time.
-(squawks)
I guess it's just easier
to hold on to the life you know
than move on
to the one you don't.
Hey, that was pretty good.
Yeah. Maybe she should be
the Spiritual Leader
of the Valley of Geese.
Whoa, that guy.
He drinks like a fish.
Should he be driving?
♪ ♪
(sizzling)
(heavy clanking)
We've come to pay tribute,
as you requested.
Looks a little light.
Go back out and get me more.
-More?
-But-but, Chameleon...
Go. Before I toss you down
another flight of stairs.
(bosses grumbling)
At last, my destiny approaches.
I'll expand my rule
from Juniper City
to every city and town
and village
from here to the Valley of Peace
and beyond.
(echoing):
They will all know the name
of The Chameleon!
ZHEN:
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up!
(screams) Zhen!
I had a vision.
I saw The Chameleon.
She's gonna take over
cities and towns
and the Valley of Peace.
A vision?
While you were asleep.
I'm pretty sure
that's just a dream.
Not a dream! A vision.
Either I had a bad dumpling
before I went to sleep
or it's a Dragon Warrior thing.
We got to get to The Chameleon
and take her down.
Well, then, you're in luck.
Welcome to Juniper City.
♪ ♪
Whoa!
ZHEN:
This is the place
where you can be
whatever you want to be,
do whatever you want to do
and steal
whatever you want to steal.
Uh, if that's your thing.
FISH:
Land ho!
(all grunting)
Whoa. That came out of nowhere.
(lively chatter)
(grunting)
(grunts)
-Whoa!
-Move! -Look out!
-Sorry.
-Out of the way!
I've never seen
so much traffic before.
ZHEN: You don't have rush hour
in the Valley of Peace?
No one's ever in
that much of a rush. (grunts)
Come on!
(exclaiming)
Well, sure is good
to be home again.
The sights, the sounds...
(sniffing)
The smells.
(gasps)
Oh...
(panting)
It's a wonton wonderland!
Hoo-hoo-hoo!
Yeah!
Whoa. (laughs)
-ZHEN: Po. Po!
-(excited panting)
Focus!
This city is the most
amazing place I've ever seen!
I used to feel the same way
until The Chameleon
got her claws into it.
-(whimpering)
-(chortling)
-(growls)
-(gasps)
-(grunts)
-(bleats weakly)
(low growling)
Tonight we take down
The Chameleon.
Oh, yeah.
I'll show you where
this villainous sorceress lurks
as she dominates the city.
Is she lurking
in that villainous tower
dominating the city?
-How'd you know?
-Eh, not my first time
taking down a villain.
-Let's keep moving.
-CITIZEN: Hey, Zhen.
-Hey-ya, Zhen.
-Long time no see.
-How you doing, Zhen?
-Wow.
-You're quite the local celeb.
-Yeah, well,
let's just say a face like mine
is hard to forget.
What?!
You're a wanted criminal?
You sound surprised.
Is this surprising?
I don't think
this is surprising.
You never mentioned
you were wanted.
Don't worry.
The law has better things to do
than look for me.
-Hey, fox.
-We've been looking for you.
-Must be a slow work week.
-I'll handle this.
Morning, Officers.
Dragon Warrior here.
The fox and I are here
on official Dragon Warrior biz.
-Dragon who?
-Warrior what?
Dragon Warrior? Anyone?
Nothing?
Perhaps you know me better as...
the Kung Fu Panda!
-Wait, wait!
-(officers laughing)
Can you believe that guy?
-Ah, come on!
-Okay.
So we tried it your way.
Now we try it mine.
Wait, what's your way?
(screaming)
(grunts) Sorry.
Come on, come on,
come on, come on!
You can't run away from the law.
You're a wanted criminal.
Yeah, well, it looks like
I'm not the only one.
Wow, city life
really is fast-paced.
We got to get out of here
before they call for...
(rumbling)
...backup.
(growling)
That's a lot of bull.
-Run!
-(exclaims)
(grunts with effort)
(grunts)
-Let's go. Let's go!
-(whimpers)
(snorts)
(growls)
(both screaming)
Ooh! Ow!
-(grunts)
-(squeals)
(exclaims)
-Whoa.
-(screams)
(vibrating grunts)
-Whoa!
-(both screaming)
-Oh!
-(both grunting)
(both gasp)
(roaring)
(screaming)
Let's go.
Whoa!
(grunts)
(all straining)
I'm falling... very slowly.
Oh!
(screaming)
(groaning)
(yells)
(grunts) Sorry.
-(grunts)
-(crying)
♪ ♪
-(panting)
-(soft tinkling)
(whimpering)
Whew.
(feet screech)
There they are!
We don't have time
for a drum solo.
We're trapped.
(both grunting)
(Po screams)
-I heard drumming.
-(confused chatter)
-It isn't much farther now.
-You always say that,
and it's always so much farther.
Whoa.
What is this place?
Home sweet home.
Some of the best crooks
and criminals
in all of Juniper City
live here.
(whirring)
Careful. These guys
will steal your pants
right off ya,
and you'll never know it.
Uh-oh. Now, you kids be careful
with those fireworks.
(snarling)
(shrieking)
Ooh.
-(shouting)
-(growling)
(grunts)
Ow!
(snarling)
BUNNIES:
Oh.
(giggling)
So you're friends
with all these people?
They're practically family.
Zhen.
Oh! Is that really you?
Han, my old mentor.
I always knew someday
you'll find your way home
back to the den.
And when you did...
(thieves growling)
...I'd be sure to give you
a proper homecoming.
-Family, huh?
-More like distant cousins.
All right,
how should we do this?
Quick and painless
or slow and painful?
(cheerily): Slow and painful.
Slow and painful.
All right, you little scamps.
Slow and painful it is.
-Yay!
-Hooray!
You really don't want
to do this.
-And why is that?
-Because if you so much as
lay one claw on me, you're
gonna have to answer to...
the Dragon Warrior.
(imitating echo):
Warrior. Warrior. Warrior.
Warrior. Warrior.
Who?
(confused chatter)
Oh, man, are my adventures
really that regional?
Introduce them, Po.
To your fists.
(thieves growling)
Remember, Po,
there are other ways
to bring peace
than by kicking butt.
Ah, come on. Really?
-Now?
-Yes, now.
Hold on. Shouldn't my inner
Shifus have differing opinions?
We are in total agreement.
With our mutual disappointment.
BOTH:
In you.
Wait.
(murmuring)
He who resorts
to violence now...
will only find
more violence later.
(confused murmuring)
So what you're saying is,
if we don't hurt Zhen
a little now...
We can hurt her a lot later.
What?
No, that's not what I said.
Yes! And more violence later
is better than
less violence now.
No, no,
I think you're misunderstanding
the fundamental point of what...
-More violence!
-Hooray!
Violence makes my tummy tingle.
You know, that panda makes
a lot of good points.
I like it.
BUNNIES (chanting):
Violence! Violence! Violence!
No, no, no, wait! Come back!
I'll come up with better wisdom.
You have got to workshop
those proverbs.
-PO: Uh, the kung fu panda?
-Nope.
The son of Mr. Ping and Li?
Those are both
very common names.
-Mentored by Oogway?
-Sorry.
Trained by Master Shifu?
-Oh, Master Shifu.
-Aha!
Yes. Everyone's heard of
the legendary Master Shifu.
But not you.
Did someone say "legendary"?
Bring it in.
Look, Han, I know
we've had our differences,
but I'm really in a jam here,
and I was hoping
you could help me out.
-Thank you.
-Don't drink that.
(sizzling)
BUNNIES:
Ooh.
(giggling)
We just need someplace
to lie low
for a while
until the heat cools off.
And why should I help you?
Because deep down, beneath that
iron-scaled exterior
is a good-hearted soul
who still thinks of me
as one of the family?
Fine. But if you're still here
by nightfall,
I'm calling the bulls myself.
Sleep tight. (laughing)
(laughter fades)
So tonight, we take down
The Chameleon.
-After you get your pants back.
-(hooting)
Not cool! You guys...
Come on! Give them back.
Those are custom.
(hooting)
Yeah, this place doesn't look
very friendly.
Oh, my tail. (groans)
I'm sure everything is fine.
This is a restaurant.
These are my people.
We speak the same language.
You wait here.
-(door opens)
-Salutations!
I'm so sorry to interrupt.
(chuckles)
I know you're having
a good time, but I was
wondering if a panda happened
to be passing by these parts?
There was a panda here.
You know him?
Know him? Why, I'm his dad.
(quacking)
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Hmm?
You need to pay for
what your son did to my tavern.
(glass shatters)
My boy wouldn't have done this
for no reason.
Is it possible
your broth was bland?
-Try it.
-(yelps)
No. No!
The broth smells excellent.
You should not add a
single thing, especially not me.
LI:
Hands off the goose.
(patrons gasping)
The panda's back.
OTHERS:
He's back?
No.
But you're about to wish he was.
'Cause if you think
he made a mess of this place,
you have no idea
what I'm capable of.
Everything he learned,
he learned from me.
Except one thing.
Mercy.
I don't know where he got that,
because I don't believe in it.
Now, this can go
one of two ways.
The easy way, in which
you tell me where he is,
or the hard way, in which
but it's hard to understand
what you're saying
-because you have no teeth.
-(gulps)
(patrons gasping)
(gasps, whimpers)
Mah-jongg.
I eat mah-jongg tiles
for breakfast!
(snarls, munches)
-Ooh.
-(growling)
(snarling)
(grunting rhythmically)
(yells)
(wood creaking)
(quacks)
(clamoring)
(gasping, murmuring)
Huh?
(wood creaking)
(chuckles)
-(panicked clamoring)
-Move! Move! Get out of my way!
(clamoring continues)
Stay there!
Where's our son?
He took a boat to Juniper City.
Which way?
You know, a wise goose once...
-Time to go.
-Uh, yeah. Right.
(sighs)
(patrons scream)
(patrons groaning, coughing)
(groans)
(cheering)
♪ ♪
(bunnies giggling)
Okay, let's try this again.
Stir the pot,
roll the wok, serve the dish,
and ska-blam!
Hey, where's the golden dragon
that's supposed to shoot out?
Not gonna happen with a broom.
That's still not bad, though.
Yeah, but stir later,
roll higher,
and the word is "skadoosh."
"Skadoosh" isn't a word.
And "ska-blam" is?
(fireworks whistling, popping)
(screaming)
BUNNIES:
Ska-blam!
(hisses, bubbles)
(sighs)
I got to say, you're not like
any of the other masters
I've met.
Yeah, I know.
There's not a lot of pandas.
No, you're, like, a good guy.
Listen up. The coast is clear.
Thieves, hit the streets.
And you two,
get out of my sight.
♪ ♪
Huh?
I know I promised
that I'd lead you
right to The Chameleon's
front door,
but the back door seems
a little more practical.
I got to say, Zhen,
you really are
a fox of your word.
A chewed-up peach pit?
One from Master Oogway's
peach tree of heavenly wisdom.
Eh, it's a Valley of Peace
thing.
It's supposed to remind me
that every pit
holds the promise
of a mighty tree.
Maybe it'll do the same for you.
Are you sure
you want to do this?
As a wise spiritual leader
once said,
"How may one kick butt if one
doesn't seek a butt to kick?"
You're a real piece of work,
you know that?
Thank you.
Wait, was that a compliment
or an insult?
ZHEN:
Yes.
(crowd chatter)
(whimpers)
Whoa.
(whimpering)
Have you seen our son?
Hmm.
(yells, pants)
-Sorry.
-No.
-(bleating): Nah.
Tell us you've seen our son.
(squawks)
Wait, why are they leaving?
You said yes.
Hey, look. Po was here.
Amazing, Li.
But how can you tell?
We pandas have a gift
for seeing what others cannot.
Come on. There may be
more clues up ahead.
-(gasps)
-(snores)
(muffled yell)
(guards snoring)
(shushes)
(gasps softly)
(clanging loudly)
(sighs) Why?
(gasps)
(guard stirring, coughs)
(sneeze building)
(gurgles, toots)
(guards snarling)
(Zhen and Po scream)
-(hissing)
-(both gasp)
(clanking, whirring)
(both yelling)
(yelling)
(prolonged grunt)
(pained grunting)
(exhales)
-That was close.
-Look out!
Huh?
-Po!
-Stand back.
(shouts)
Whoa.
(footsteps marching)
-They're coming.
-Hurry, help me lift the cage.
(both straining)
(exhales) It's no use.
We got to brace it
with something.
Here, use my staff.
All right. Stand back.
Here I go.
Zhen?
Where are you taking my staff?
I think you mean my staff.
You gave it to Zhen,
and now Zhen has given it to me.
"Given to gain,"
I believe, is how it works.
You were right, Zhen.
He was an easy mark.
Zhen.
First rule of the streets:
never trust anyone.
(chuckles) I taught her that.
And you thought my apprentice
was your friend?
Apprentice?
She's the one that took you in?
Best thing that
ever happened to her.
You should have seen
the little guttersnipe
before I found her.
Mangy and half starved.
Hanging out with those rejects
from the Den of Thieves.
(gasps)
(yells, strains)
She had no fear.
Such potential.
So I took her in.
I made her what she is today.
-Stand up straight.
-Yes, Master.
So you went through all of this
just to get me to give you
the Staff of Wisdom. Why?
I, too, came from
humble beginnings
and dreamed of becoming
something more.
I wanted respect and power.
I wanted to be
a master of kung fu.
-Say what?
-I was turned away
from every training hall
I went to.
They would say
I was too small, too lowly
and that kung fu
was not my destiny.
And so I chose a different path:
(deeper voice):
sorcery.
I grew.
I excelled.
And I got everything
I had ever dreamed of.
Everything except kung fu.
-(roars)
-(yelps)
Just because I can look
like Tai Lung doesn't mean
I can fight like him.
(normal voice):
You see, Po,
kung fu may be performed
by the body,
but its secrets are housed
in the spirit.
And now that I have access
to the Spirit Realm...
You're gonna steal
Tai Lung's kung fu.
His and those of every master
villain that came before me.
And once I do, no one will dare
underestimate me again.
You forgot about me.
(grunting fiercely)
(laughs) Don't bother, Po.
Those bars are enchanted
with some very old
and very powerful magic.
You'd need at least ten Dragon
Warriors to get through them.
Then I won't go through them.
I'll go under them.
(yelling)
(screams, groans)
(grunts)
(weapons clanging)
(low growling)
Well, that's frustrating
for all sorts of reasons.
(muffled, distorted grunting)
(grunting)
(panting)
Ah!
(door creaking)
(guards yelling)
(grunts)
-(guards yelling)
-(panting)
(grunting)
(screeches)
(both screaming)
-ZHEN: Po!
-Zhen?
-My staff. Hand it over.
-I'm so sorry I lied to you.
I-I was just doing
what I was told.
Apologize later. Right now
I have to stop The Chameleon.
Po!
Zhen?
(laughing)
(panting)
-(growls)
-(screaming)
No!
(screaming fades)
Well done, Zhen.
You never said
you were gonna hurt him.
What's the second rule
of the streets?
Someone always gets hurt.
And make sure it's never you.
I just wish there had been
another way.
-Third rule of the streets?
-Third rule?
Some would say
it's the most important.
No one is interested
in your feelings.
Chop-chop.
We have a Spirit Realm
to plunder.
And smile.
Nobody likes a grouch.
Honestly, Zhen,
I don't know where
you pick up such bad habits.
(grunting)
(whimpers)
Oh, if I could...
(snarling)
Hey there.
(shouts) Whoa!
-(branch cracks)
-(straining)
Get off me. Ow. Ow. Ah!
-(screams, whimpers)
-(snarling)
-(gasps)
-PING: Son!
(yells)
(grunting rhythmically)
(screaming)
-Now save me.
-(grunts)
Ah!
-Hi, son.
-(branch snapping)
(both scream)
It's okay. We've got you, Po.
We've got you.
(wind whistling)
PO:
So you followed me?
-It was his idea.
-(grumbles)
Okay, okay.
It was both our ideas.
We only follow because we love.
No, you followed because
you didn't believe in me.
And because we love?
Well, you're right.
I screwed up big-time.
I trusted the wrong person.
I gave the Staff of Wisdom
right to The Chameleon.
Oh.
Po...
that was
a very big-time screwup.
If only I'd listened
to Master Shifu
and stayed in
the Valley of Peace,
The Chameleon
wouldn't have my staff
and none of this
would be happening.
I was just so determined to
keep things the way they were.
Everyone is afraid
of change, Po.
Even me.
There was a time,
not so long ago,
when all I wanted to be
was the greatest noodle chef
in the valley.
So what happened?
I became the greatest
noodle chef in the valley.
-It's true.
-But I also became a father.
And nothing... nothing's
ever been the same since.
Change doesn't always
have to be a bad thing.
Why do you think
I always change the menu
at the restaurant?
Because if things stayed
the same forever,
sooner or later,
they would lose their flavor.
He's right, Po.
Since I left my village,
I've become a bit of a warrior.
Strong. Brave.
-(whip cracks)
-(whimpers)
-GUARD: Move it. This way.
-(whip cracks)
Get those cages up there.
Come on.
Mm. This looks bad.
-Really bad.
-GUARD: Move it!
-(whip cracks)
-Come on.
Don't tell me
you were actually starting
to become friends
with that panda.
What? No. I-It's just...
When we want something,
we must use
whatever is at our disposal
to get it.
That's all that panda was,
something to use.
Is that why you took me in?
So I could help you get
what you wanted?
Zhen, I took you in
because you were clever
and ruthless and unsentimental.
Like me.
And the day you stop being
those things
is the day when, yes,
you stop being useful to me.
So for both of our sakes,
don't change.
(latches clacking)
Tonight,
when the blood moon rises
to its highest point
in the night sky,
I will open the door
to the Spirit Realm,
and all of its secrets
will be mine!
(breathes heavily)
Does a blood moon always rise
this slowly?
I seem to remember it
rising faster.
No? Just me?
Hmm.
Ugh.
It's just for
dramatic effect anyway.
(scoffs) I think I'm just gonna
open the Spirit Realm now.
(whooshing)
♪ ♪
Bring me Tai Lung!
(roaring)
(panting, growling)
Tai Lung.
Big fan.
Who are you, and what are you
doing with that staff?
This was given to me
by an old friend of yours.
The puffy panda? (scoffs)
Po might be an idiot,
but he'd never willingly
hand over Oogway's staff
to the likes of you.
Who said anything
about willingly?
(mechanical rumbling)
Hmm.
Apparently,
I misjudged you, lizard.
Now, why have you
brought me back?
I summoned you here
so that you could teach me
your most legendary
kung fu moves.
I don't share my skills
with anyone.
It wasn't a request.
(whooshing)
(guards hissing)
(grunting)
(yells)
(Tai Lung yelling)
(roars)
(growls)
(yells)
(grunts)
♪ ♪
(growls)
(distorted grunt)
Yes, I got it.
The Tai Lung Nerve Strike.
The power, the precision.
(guards cheering weakly)
(breathing heavily)
What have you done to me?
All of your kung fu is now mine.
And the best part is,
I'm just getting warmed up.
Bring me General Kai.
(bellows)
Bring me Master Osprey.
Master Bull.
(thunder rumbles)
Po, wait! Please be reasonable.
I'm not going anywhere
until I get my staff back.
No staff is worth your life.
As long as I'm still
the Dragon Warrior,
I won't let anyone else get hurt
because of me.
(thunder rumbling)
(panting)
(gasps)
Po!
You're alive.
Please. I made a mistake.
So did I: trusting you.
I'm sorry.
Did your master tell you
to say that, too?
She's not my master.
I'm leaving, for good.
It's the truth.
I was wrong about everything.
-(grunts)
-What are you doing?
Stopping you.
Get out of my way, Zhen.
No.
Move.
You want me to move? Move me.
First you betray me,
and now you want to fight me?
-(grunting)
-Why are you doing this?
To stop you from getting killed.
(grunting)
(exclaims)
(thunder crashes)
(both breathing heavily)
What do you care
if I get killed or not?
(thunder rumbling)
Please, Po,
just let me do one thing right.
You're not the only one who's
made some bad choices lately.
You're really gonna go through
with this, aren't you?
Fraid so.
And there's nothing
I can do to talk you out of it?
I'm afraid not.
You can't beat her, you know.
You're probably right.
But I have to try.
Get as far away from this place
as you can.
-Po!
-We should never have
let him come here.
We are such terrible fathers.
At least you didn't lie
and betray him.
Well, that's true. You're worse.
I am a terrible friend.
"Friend"? That feels
a little generous, no?
Uh, l-let's just give up.
Surrender.
We can't let him go
in there alone.
What can we do?
There are just three of us
against an army.
Then I guess we'll just
have to get an army of our own.
(chitters)
-(screeching)
-(hooting)
(clamoring)
Hey! Listen up, everybody!
(inhales deeply)
-(echoing): Quack!
-(clamoring stops)
Thank you.
The Dragon Warrior's in trouble.
Who?
You know, Po.
The panda.
No, no, a different panda.
-I'm his father.
-I'm also his father.
Okay, that doesn't matter.
What matters is that
my friend's in trouble
and he needs my help.
So, I need yours.
-Why should we help you?
-Because...
Because...
it's the right thing to do.
(laughter)
Stop it! Stop! Stop laughing!
Look, I know
you think it might be
too late for a bunch of cheats,
thieves and cutthroats like us
to change our ways.
But a good friend once told me
it's never too late
to do the right thing.
So what you're saying is,
the more right we do now,
the more wrong we can do later.
-What? No.
-(thieves murmuring)
And with The Chameleon
out of the way...
We can finally do
all the wrong we want.
I-I think you're missing
the fundamental point.
(chanting):
Violence! Violence! Violence!
(Zhen sighs)
Are you guys ready
to do the right thing
-for the wrong reasons?
-(cheering)
Now, you see, the mistake
this Dragon Warrior fellow made
was underestimating
his opponent.
I never would have walked into
such an obvious trap.
-PO: Hey.
-(guards gasp)
Now, you see, the mistake
this Dragon Warrior fellow
made was...
Shut up, Larry.
This place is crawling
with more guards
than I've ever seen.
I'm never gonna get
to Po in time.
You just get to Po.
We'll take care of the guards.
We will? (chuckles nervously)
I-I mean, we will.
But how?
Just leave that to me.
(whooshing)
(cries out)
(grunts)
(shouts)
(groans)
-(grunts)
-(squeals)
(snorts)
(roars)
(grunts)
♪ ♪
PO:
General Kai?
Lord Shen?
Those are all my old nemesis-es.
Nemes-ee? Nemes-i?
The Chameleon is pulling spirits
from the Spirit Realm and
draining us of all our moves.
And she's using your staff
to do it.
-I'm here to get it back.
-(scoffs)
I won't hold my breath.
Um, I'm sorry. Do I know you?
Do you know me? It's Scott.
The fire-breathing crocodile.
(coughing) Oh, right. Scott.
Master Shifu and I were
just talking about you.
TAI LUNG:
Panda.
Oogway made a mistake choosing
you as the Dragon Warrior.
I just didn't realize how big
a mistake it was until now.
Whoa. Tai Lung?
I'm gonna get that staff back,
restore your kung fu,
and return you all
back to the Spirit Realm.
You'll see.
All I see is a broken promise.
(gate clacking)
LI:
All right,
you bunch of
cantankerous Komodos.
Now, this can go
one of two ways.
The easy way, in which
you surrender willingly,
or the hard way,
where you surrender woundedly.
The choice is yours.
-(guards snarling)
-I was kidding! I was kidding!
(screaming)
Aw.
(screeching)
(guards grunting, screaming)
(yelping)
-Thanks, Ping.
-(screaming)
Run away!
(grunting)
Cannonball!
(guard grunts)
-(laughing)
-(guards grunting)
-(slurps)
-Oh. Is it too spicy?
Mm-mm. No.
It's got the perfect kick.
Ginseng.
That's the secret
to my mulberry punch.
(clamoring)
That panda was right.
More violence later is better.
BUNNIES:
Yay!
PO: I believe you have something
that belongs to me.
Can't you even die right?
Can't you even kill wrong?
No. (chuckles)
Wordplay didn't come together.
Now, about that staff...
Take it.
I already have everything I need
from it anyway.
I think this was destiny.
A final face-off
between formidable adversaries,
alike in so many ways.
If only I had a dumpling
for every time
a villain told me
how much we had in common.
It's true. We've both risen
to the highest of heights.
It's a shame only one of us
can come out on top.
It is a shame.
For you.
THE CHAMELEON:
My combined powers
of sorcery and kung fu
make me unstoppable.
And once I dispense with you,
I'll expand my rule
from Juniper City to...
Every other city
and town and village
from here to
the Valley of Peace and beyond.
Yeah, I know.
But how did you know?
I saw it in a vision.
'Cause I'm the Dragon Warrior.
For now, at least.
But I've realized that it's
probably time I made a change.
And so should you.
I'm The Chameleon.
I do nothing but change.
Only on the outside.
Real change happens from within.
And if we're really as alike
as you say,
then maybe we could both
let go of who we were
and become something better
than we already are.
What do you say?
I say...
(screeches)
(grunts)
Well, I saw that coming.
We're very proud of you.
You tried it our way.
Now try it yours.
BOTH:
Kick her butt.
I'm way ahead of you.
(grunting)
(grunts) Hmm?
Master Elephant's Trunk Twist?
Master Boar's Tusks of Terror!
Master Wolf's Fangs of Fury!
(screams)
(barks)
(bellows)
Ooh. Master Bull's
Horns of Doom!
(growling)
What?
(distorted):
Recognize this move?
(screams)
(panting)
Is that how I sound?
I don't sound like that, do I?
PO:
You didn't earn those skills!
You just stole 'em!
(grunting)
Give him a left.
A right. Uppercut.
-Which one are you rooting for?
-I'm not sure.
This is all very confusing.
I'm stronger than every opponent
you've ever faced,
because I am every opponent
you've ever faced.
Po! (yelling)
(yell fading)
(growls)
(chuckles nervously)
(clangs)
(grunts)
Whoa. I got to workshop
those heroic entrances.
Nah. It was just right.
(grunting)
(distorted):
I knew I should've left you
to rot in the gutter
where you belong.
Better to rot in the gutter
than under your thumb.
(grunts, blows)
(grunts)
BOTH:
Hi-yah!
Two against one?
Well, now,
that doesn't seem fair.
I'll have to even the odds.
(distorted):
Master Cobra.
Master Osprey.
(echoing):
Master Scorpion.
Master Wolf.
General Kai.
Lord Shen.
(deep, distorted laugh)
That is awesome!
I mean, it's disturbing,
but it's awesome.
(roaring)
(shouts)
Whoa!
(screams)
(roaring)
Whoa!
Zhen!
(yelling)
(pained roaring)
Whoa, whoa!
(roaring)
(yelling)
(grunting)
(groans)
Po!
(distorted cackling)
(distorted):
I thought we were friends.
(gasps)
Stand back.
I'm gonna kick my butt.
(explosive booming)
(grunts)
Yah!
(grunting)
Whoa!
(yelling)
(distorted laughing)
(feet screech)
(sizzling)
(screams)
(blowing)
(grunting)
(grunting fiercely)
-Come on, Po. Get out of there.
-You have to do this.
I can't beat The Chameleon.
A wise old tortoise once told me
that you never know
what you can do until you do it.
The fate of the world
hangs in the balance,
and you're here giving me
life advice from a tortoise?
Be the pit, Zhen.
Be the pit.
♪ ♪
And what do you think
you're doing?
Finishing what Po started.
Oh, please. How many times
do I have to tell you?
(grunts)
Don't slouch.
(gasping)
(grunting)
You ungrateful little urchin!
After all I've done for you,
you betray me for the panda?
First rule of the streets:
never trust anyone.
Ha! You can't defeat me.
I know all your moves.
Not this one.
Roll, stir,
serve and ska-blam!
(roaring)
(screams)
-(cheering)
-(laughing) Yes!
Second rule:
someone always gets hurt.
Now, that's a cool move.
Po. You could've gotten out of
that cage anytime you wanted?
You faker.
It's not faking. It's Method.
Besides, how's a peach pit
ever supposed to become a tree
if you never give it
the chance to grow?
And, hey, you stirred faster
and rolled higher.
But for the last time,
the word is...
(growling)
(grunts)
..."skadoosh."
(explosive whooshing)
♪ ♪
(low growl)
Maybe Oogway was right
about you.
You aren't completely useless
after all.
Oh, my gosh, thank you so much.
(thieves cheering)
(laughs) That's my son!
Our son!
I think it's time
you send us home, panda.
(whooshing)
♪ ♪
Zhen, do something!
Third rule:
no one's interested
in your feelings.
See you on the other side,
Dragon Warrior.
(The Chameleon screams)
♪ ♪
We packed some food
for your time in jail.
Let's hope it's not
your final meal.
Thanks, guys.
I was thinking.
After I serve my time
and I'm a free fox again,
maybe I'll open
one of those acupuncture places
-that are all the rage.
-I think you're better suited
for a job with
a little more room for growth.
Jade Palace?
(sputters) Her?
Out of all the candidates
you choose to train
as your worthy successor,
you chose the fox?
You know when you know.
You know?
Fine, choose who you want.
A thief, a stick, a carrot.
I don't even know why I bother.
I'm going to go meditate,
a lot.
Don't worry. He'll come around.
Probably.
Maybe.
Hey.
You okay?
(sighs) He's right.
What about me says
I'm ready for this?
Well, as I learned from working
in my dad's kitchen,
sometimes the greatest dishes
come from
the most unlikely ingredients.
Hey, that's not bad.
Okay, I see you,
Spiritual Leader.
Yeah. I'm getting the hang of
this proverb thing.
One shouldn't do a deep squat
with a chopstick
in one's pocket.
You know, maybe you should
just stick to kicking butt.
Money can't buy happiness.
But it sure can buy
a lot of dumplings.
Why does it always come back
to dumplings with you?
When life gives you lemons,
make pear juice
and blow everyone's minds.
We get it.
You can't have your mooncake
and eat it, too.
Although, I guess
you could have mooncake
and then order mango pudding
on the side.
ZHEN: Can we just start
the training now?
Inner peace.
Inner peace. Inner peace.
Hey, Master Shifu.
-Look, there's two of us.
-You're doing great, Shifu.
You're not breathing
with your belly.
-You look a little tired.
-Are you tired?
(voices overlapping)
-You do look like a squirrel.
-Do you want a cookie?
(screams)
(panting)
(sighs) Inner peace.
Inner peace.
("...Baby One More Time"
by Tenacious D playing)
Are you ready
to begin your training?
Are you?
Yes.
And I brought a little help.
♪ Oh, baby, baby,
how was I supposed to know ♪
Whoa.
♪ That something
wasn't right here? ♪
-♪ Oh, baby, baby ♪
-Hi-yah! Hi-yah!
♪ I shouldn't have let you go ♪
Oh! Oh! Hot! Hot, hot!
♪ And now
you're out of sight, yeah ♪
♪ Show me
how you want it to be ♪
Oh... Whoa!
♪ Yeah, tell me, baby ♪
♪ 'Cause I need to know
now because ♪
♪ My loneliness is killing me ♪
♪ And I ♪
♪ I must confess ♪
♪ I still believe ♪
♪ Still believe ♪
♪ When I'm not with you,
I lose my mind ♪
♪ Give me a sign ♪
♪ Hit me, baby, one more time ♪
-♪ Oh, baby, baby ♪
-(laughs)
-♪ The reason I breathe is you ♪
-(screaming)
♪ Girl, you've got me blinded ♪
-♪ Oh, pretty baby ♪
-(yelling)
♪ There's nothing
that I wouldn't do ♪
♪ It's not the way
I planned it ♪
♪ Show me ♪
♪ How you want it to be ♪
-♪ Yeah, tell me, baby ♪
-(chuckles)
♪ 'Cause I need to know
now because ♪
♪ My loneliness is killing me ♪
♪ And I ♪
♪ I must confess
I still believe ♪
♪ Still believe ♪
♪ When I'm not with you,
I lose my mind ♪
♪ Give me a sign ♪
♪ Hit me, baby, one more time ♪
♪ B-B-Baby, baby,
ba-baby, b-b-baby ♪
♪ Hit me one more time ♪
♪ Hit me ♪
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
-♪ One more time ♪
-♪ Hit me ♪
♪ Oh, ba-a-a... ♪
♪ Now, hit me, baby,
but not too hard ♪
♪ Hit me one more time ♪
♪ Hit me, baby,
but not too hard ♪
♪ One more time again ♪
♪ Oh, baby, baby,
how was I supposed to know ♪
♪ That something
wasn't right here? ♪
♪ Oh, pretty baby ♪
♪ I shouldn't have let you go ♪
♪ And I must confess ♪
♪ That my loneliness ♪
♪ Is killing me now ♪
♪ Don't you know ♪
♪ I still believe ♪
♪ That you will be here ♪
♪ And give me a sign ♪
♪ Hit me, baby, one more time ♪
♪ My loneliness is killing me ♪
♪ And I ♪
♪ I must confess ♪
♪ I still believe ♪
♪ Still believe ♪
♪ When I'm not with you,
I lose my mind ♪
♪ Give me a sign ♪
♪ Hit me, baby, one more time. ♪
(song ends)
♪ ♪
(music ends)